Emmanuel Sauceda

1667 N Nydia Avenue San Luis, AZ 85349 (928) 323-7266 Emmanuelsauceda9@gmail.com

SKILLS

I have a wide range of skills: being hard-working, organized, independent, competent, and efficient. Along with that I can speak and write both English and Spanish fluently. I've also worked along multiple teams to build many engineering projects, allowing me to use my mathematical skills to the fullest and learn from all the experiences. I have maintained consistent A's and B's throughout all my high school years. I am also able to learn new tasks quickly and work around any problem that is presented. Along with that I also have exemplary customer service skills.

EXPERIENCE

Phoenix, Az - Car cleaner/assistant

May 2021 - August 2021 I assist my brother in his workshop. I helped clean and detail cars along with organizing tools.

San Luis, AZ - Customer Loyalty Group - ACT

June 2022 - August 2022

I was part of the customer service retention group in which we focused on retaining customers who wanted to quit their contract with us as well as help them solve their problems to satisfy their needs.

Somerton,AZ — Retail Service Specialist

November 2022 - Present

My main focus was on assisting customer's issue as well as providing them with the best service possible.

EDUCATION

School Name, San Luis High School- High School Diploma

August 2018 - May 2022 SkillsUSA member FFA Member GPA 3.6

Roger William University - Summer Program

June 2019- July 2019

Attended 3 week program on University level engineering. During this I acquired professional math skills used in the real world.

SKILLS

Advance Computer skills
welding / welding tools
Welding knowledge
Engineering knowledge
Cleaning skills
Organizing skills
Bilingual (English/Spanish)
Advance math knowledge

AWARDS/CERTIFICATION

Engineering Certification

OSHA 10 Hour General Industry Card

John Hopkins "CTY" Certificate

LANGUAGES

Fluent Spanish speaking and writing

Fluent English speaking and writing

REFERENCES

Cesar Martinez — O'reilly Store Manager (928) 388-4297

Marco Covarrubias — O'reilly Commercial suppervisor

Carlos Garcia — English teacher (928)750-1922